<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liz &amp; Conor&#39;s Wedding</title>
    <link>localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liz &amp; Conor&#39;s Wedding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:16:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/accommodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:16:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/accommodation/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of great accommodation options in Victoria &amp;mdash; here are a few suggestions. Note that the Friday night drinks will be in downtown Victoria, and on Saturday we will arrange a bus from the DoubleTree hotel to the Beach House and back.
DoubleTree by Hilton We have arranged a 15% discount for wedding guests at the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel &amp;amp; Suites Victoria between 25-29 April. The discount is applied to the best available rate at the time of booking, using this booking link or by calling +1 250 940 3106 with the reference &amp;lsquo;P99 rate on April 25, 2019&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to Do</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/things-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/things-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We have listed some sightseeing ideas and useful links below.
 Victoria sightseeing Vancouver sightseeing British Columbia tourism Indigenous Tourism BC Victoria Ale Trail Butchart Gardens Whale watching Skiing at Whistler-Blackcomb (Blackcomb mountain remains open until mid-May)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 16:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Here</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/getting-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 11:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/getting-here/</guid>
      <description>Electronic Travel Authorization Guests coming from Ireland, the UK and other visa-exempt countries will need an Electronic Travel Authorization (eTA). You can apply for an eTA on the Government of Canada website. The application process costs CAD $7 and only takes a few minutes.
Flights Airports The most convenient airports for Victoria are listed below.
 Victoria International Airport (YYJ) (approx. 35 minutes from the city centre by shuttle bus)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 10:42:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/events/</guid>
      <description>Friday 26 April 2019 8 - 11 pm (TBC) Finger food and drinks in downtown Victoria
 Venue to be confirmed  Saturday 27 April 2019 Afternoon (Time to be confirmed) Wedding ceremony at St David&amp;rsquo;s Church, Cordova Bay
 St David&amp;rsquo;s is a 20 minute drive from downtown Victoria A bus will take guests from the DoubleTree hotel to St David&amp;rsquo;s  Evening (until 12:30 am) Reception at the Beach House, Cordova Bay</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>