<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liz &amp; Conor&#39;s Wedding</title>
    <link>https://lizandconor.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liz &amp; Conor&#39;s Wedding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 20:10:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lizandconor.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to Do</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/things-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 20:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/things-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We have listed some sightseeing ideas and useful links below.
 Victoria sightseeing Victoria hiking Vancouver sightseeing Vancouver hiking British Columbia sightseeing Indigenous Tourism BC Sea to Sky Gondola, Squamish, BC Victoria Ale Trail Butchart Gardens, Victoria Whale watching Skiing at Whistler-Blackcomb Banff and Lake Louise, Alberta  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 11:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/gifts/</guid>
      <description>We are very lucky to have friends and family travelling from near and far to celebrate with us, and your presence is the perfect gift!!
However we have been asked by a few guests for gift ideas. We would be very grateful for contributions towards our honeymoon or our upcoming home renovations (both are currently in the planning stages!). We have also prepared a wedding registry with Hudson&amp;rsquo;s Bay department store which you can access here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/accommodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:16:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/accommodation/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of great accommodation options in Victoria &amp;mdash; here are a few suggestions. Note that the Friday night drinks will be in downtown Victoria, and on Saturday we will arrange a bus from the DoubleTree hotel to the Beach House and back.
DoubleTree by Hilton We have arranged a 15% discount for wedding guests at the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel &amp;amp; Suites Victoria between 25-29 April. The discount is applied to the best available rate at the time of booking, using this booking link or by calling +1 250 940 3106 with the reference &amp;lsquo;P99 rate on April 25, 2019&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 16:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Here</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/getting-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 11:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/getting-here/</guid>
      <description>Electronic Travel Authorization Guests coming from Ireland, the UK and other visa-exempt countries will need an Electronic Travel Authorization (eTA). You can apply for an eTA on the Government of Canada website. The application process costs CAD $7 and only takes a few minutes.
Visitors to the USA may need to apply for an ESTA.
Flights Airports The most convenient airports for Victoria are listed below.
 Victoria International Airport (YYJ) (approx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://lizandconor.com/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 10:42:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizandconor.com/events/</guid>
      <description>Friday 26 April 2019 Welcome Drinks Join us for drinks and appetizers at 10 Acres Bistro Bar from 8:30 pm onwards.
Saturday 27 April 2019 Wedding Ceremony Our wedding ceremony will be at St David by-the-Sea Anglican Church, and will start at 3:30 pm.
 St David&amp;rsquo;s is a 20 minute drive from downtown Victoria Guests taking the coach should come to the DoubleTree hotel lobby at 2:30 pm. The coach will depart at 2:40 pm sharp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>